The Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection 1903-2012 (Bulk 1970-2000) MSS 040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize: Series II: Graphic Material
  - Subseries B: Posters
    - Cambridge (UK) Animation Film Festival, 1981 (Box [map case], Folder 3)
    - Fischinger: A Retrospective of HisPaintings & Films, Gallery 609, Denver, 1980 (Box [map case], Folder 4)
    - Independent Cinema, Film Forum, Winter 1977, New York, 1977 (Box [map case], Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art FilmBulletin, Oct. & Nov. 1977(?) (Box [map case], Folder 6)
    - NewAmerican Filmmakers Series, Whitney Museum of Art, New York, Fall 1975 (Box [map case], Folder 7)
    - New American Filmmakers Series,Whitney Museum of Art, New York, Winter 1975/76, 1975-1976 (Box [map case], Folder 8)
    - 19th International Tournee of Animation, 1986 (Box [map case], Folder 9)
    - Oskar Fischinger: "The WorkingProcess", Theatre Vanguard, Los Angeles, 1976 (Box [map case], Folder 10)
    - Oskar Fischinger Programma, Melkweg Cinema, Amsterdam (Holland), n.d., undated (Box [map case], Folder 11)
    - The Walter Lantz Conference onAnimation, Los Angeles, 1987 (Box [map case], Folder 12)
    - The2nd Annual Walter Lantz Conference on Animation, Los Angeles, 1988 (Box [map case], Folder 13)
    - The Television Laboratory at Thirteen, 1972-1984 (Box [map case], Folder 14)
    - UBU, an Animated Film by GeoffDunbar, n.d., undated (Box [map case], Folder 15)
    - WarnerBros. Cartoons Golden Jubilee, Museum of Modern Art, New York, 1985-1986 (Box [map case], Folder 16)
    - THE WIZARD'S SON, 1981 (8) (Box [map case], Folder 17)
- Accretions 2000 - Series I: Documentary Material
  Documentary material includes interview transcripts, research notes, correspondence, film production drafts and outlines, news articles and promotional materials.
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - Disney Institute press kit, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dreamworks Studios: PRINCE OF EGYPT, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 22nd Annual Annie Awards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Warner Brothers Studios: IRON GIANT, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Algar, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Allers, Roger, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Anderson, Ken, undated (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
    - Baer, Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Barks, Carl, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Barrier, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Baytos, Betsy, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bell, Carl, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bertino, Al, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Bluth, Don, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bodrero, Jim, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bosson, Jack: Notes from Story Development Workshop, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Brightman, Homer, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Brizzi, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Canemaker, John: Paper Dreams, undated (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
    - Champion, Marge, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Chapman, Brenda, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Clemmons, Larry, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Coates, Claude, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Codrick, Tom, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Colvig, Pinto, undated (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
    - Cottrell, Bill, undated (Box 1, Folder 32-33)
    - Crump, Roland, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Culhane, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - DaGradi, Don, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - DeBlois, Dean, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Deja, Andreas, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Disney, Roy O., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Disney, Walt: Employee Evaluations, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Disney, Walt: Memos - miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Disney, Walt: Personnel Data - miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Disney, Walt: Studio strike, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - ALICE IN WONDERLAND, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - Animation Drafts (various), undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - BAMBI, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - BAND CONCERT, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE BRAVE LITTLE TAILOR, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - COUNTRY COUSIN, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - GODDESS OF SPRING, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - HOW TO... (various titles featuring Goofy), undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - JUNGLE BOOK, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - KINGDOM OF THE SUN, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - LADY AND THE TRAMP, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Disney, Walt: Lecia reel memo, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE LITTLE WHIRLWIND, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - MAKE MINE MUSIC, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE OLD MILL, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - 101 DALMATIONS, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - PETER PAN, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - PINOCCHIO, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THE RESCUERS, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SNOW WHITE AND THE SEVEN DWARFS, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SORCERER'S APPRENTICE, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - SWORD IN THE STONE, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - THREE CABALLEROS, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Disney, Walt: Films - WYNKEN, BLYNKEN AND NOD, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Disney-Miller, Diane, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Engel, Jules, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Ewing, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Fallberg, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Ferguson, Norm, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Fischinger, Oscar, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Fujikawa, Gyo, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Gerry, Vance, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Gillett, Burt, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Gombert, Ed, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Grant, Campbell, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Hansen, Ed, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Harkey, Kevin, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Haskett, Dan, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Hee, T. (Thorton), undated (Box 2, Folder 83-84)
    - Horvath, Ferdinand, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Huemer, Dick, undated (Box 2, Folder 86-88)
    - Hurd, Earl, undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Husband, Ron, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Ising, Rudy, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Iwerks, Ub, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Jackson, Wilfred, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Johnson, Barry, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Jones, Volus, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Keane, Glen, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Kelsey, Dick, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Kinney, Jack, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Kley, Heinrich, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Legg, J. Gordon, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Luske, Ham, undated (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Lyons, Michael, undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Mattinson, Burny, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Michener, Dave, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Miller, Jack, undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Natwick, Grim, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Noble, Maurice, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - O'Connor, Ken, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Oliver, Dale, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Peet, Bill, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Penner, Erdman, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Peterson, Ken, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Petty, Sara, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Plummer, Elmer, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Pomeroy, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Provensen, Martin, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Putnam, Thor, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Ranft, Joe, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Reeves, Harry, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Richmond, Neil, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Rinaldi, Joe, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Ring, Borge, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Salkin, Leo, undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Sanders, Chris, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Schumacher, Thomas, undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Scott, Retta, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Sears, Ted, undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Sharpstein, Ben, undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Shaw, Mel, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Sito, Tom, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Smith, David, undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Smith, Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Smith, Webb, undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Southworth, Ken, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Stallings, George, undated (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Sterner, Robert, undated (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Takamoto, Iwao, undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Thomas, Bob: Art of Animation, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 138-139)
    - Trousdale, Gary, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Weeks, Clair, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - West, Tiger, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Wightman, Kelly, undated (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Williams, Chris, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Williams, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Williams, Roy, undated (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Wise, Kirk, undated (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Wong, Tyrus, undated (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Young, Cy, undated (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Young, Pete, undated (Box 4, Folder 150)
- Accretions 2000 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries B: People
    - Barks, Carl, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Accretions 2001 - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - Disney Action Analysis Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - United Productions of America, undated (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Babbitt, Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - Babbitt, Art, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - Messmer, Otto, undated (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
    - Messmer, Otto, undated (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
    - Tissa, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Accretions 2001 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - United Productions of America: Mr. Boing Boing, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Accretions 2001 - Oversize - Series II: GraphicMaterial
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork
    - Hubley, John and Faith, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Messmer, Otto: Felix the Cat, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Tissa, David (original pencil sketches), undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Unknown artist, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Accretions 2003 - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - Animal Sketching (photocopy), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Animation Storyboarding, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Union Portfolio Folder, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Disney: Assorted Animation Brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Disney: Assorted Production Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Disney: Assorted Production Meeting Transcripts, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Animation Research (news clippings), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - General Animation Research (notes), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - General Art Research, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Mousetrap (photocopy of off-the-record drawings by Disney artists), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Canemaker, John: AIDS Dance-a-thon, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Canemaker, John: Angels on Ice, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Canemaker, John: Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Canemaker, John: The Art of the Hubleys, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Canemaker, John: Authored Press (various articles), 1972-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Canemaker, John: Awards, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Canemaker, John: Before the Animation Begins, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Canemaker, John: Biographical material, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Canemaker, John: BOTTOM'S DREAM, undated (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Canemaker, John: BREAK THE SILENCE, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Canemaker, John: BRIDGEHAMPTON, undated (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - Canemaker, John: Chemical Abstracts (Kaz), undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Canemaker, John: CONFESSIONS OF A STAND-UP, undated (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
    - Canemaker, John: CONFESSIONS OF A STAR DREAMER, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Department of the Army, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Film Festival-related, 1973-1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1974-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: Ninomiya, Yoko, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Canemaker, John: The Creative Spirit, undated (Box 1, Folder 32-33)
    - Canemaker, John: Dennis Blair Folder, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (DVD commentary), undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (DVD commentary), undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Canemaker, John: DUMBO (story outline), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Canemaker, John: Felix: the Twisted Tale..., undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Canemaker, John: Film Festivals (various programs and brochures), undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Canemaker, John: FOCUS Awards, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Canemaker, John: Grant Supporting Material, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Canemaker, John: Hiroshima '85 (film festival), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Canemaker, John: How to get Blessed Without Sneezing, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Canemaker, John: JOHN LENNON SCKETCHBOOK, undated (Box 2, Folder 47-48)
    - Canemaker, John: The MacDowell Colony Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Canemaker, John: Marymount Manhattan College Alumni Recognition Award, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Canemaker, John: Marymount Manhattan College President's Report, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Canemaker, John: PAPER DREAMS, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1959-1979 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Clippings (articles about J.C.), undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Canemaker, John: Press Releases, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Canemaker, John: PS 1: Animations, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Canemaker, John: Request, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Canemaker, John: SNOW WHITE (DVD commentary), undated (Box 2, Folder 60-61)
    - Canemaker, John: Tex Avery: The Great Animation Director, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DO CHILDREN THINK..., undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Canemaker, John: Winsor McCay: His Life and Art, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SUN, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Canemaker, John: Woman of the Year, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON'T HAVE TO DIE, undated (Box 2, Folder 68-70)
    - Charlot, Jean, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt (biographical material - Missouri), undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Ewing, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Graham, Don, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Graham, Don: The Art of Animation, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 75-76)
    - Grant, Joe, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Keane, Glen, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Kentridge, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Lasseter, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Mitchell, Mark, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Moore, Fred, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Peterson, Ken, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Williams, Richard, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Williams, Richard: Master Class Lectures, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 85-86)
    - Williams, Richard: photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Williams, Richard: promotional materials, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Williams, Richard: Raggedy Ann and Andy (original script with annotations), undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Williams, Richard: Raggedy Ann and Andy (slides and photographs), undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Accretions 2003 - Series II: Graphic Material
  Conditions Governing Access
  One file in Series II Subseries A has been restricted by the collection donor. This file will become avaiable to researchers in March 2023.
  Unless otherwise noted, graphic materials are copies of originals.
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork
    - Blair, Mary: ALICE IN WONDERLAND, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Blair, Mary: from Animated Research Lab (ARL), undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Blair, Mary: assorted, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Blair, Mary: CINDERELLA, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Blair, Mary: commercial artwork, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Blair, Mary: It's a Small World, undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Blair, Mary: from Kevin Blair Collection, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Blair, Mary: PETER PAN, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Blair, Mary: Personal art and greeting cards, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Blair, Mary: from Walt Disney Art Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Clark, Les, undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Gabriel, Mike, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Grant, Joe, undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 4, Folder 118-119)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated (Box 4, Folder 123-124)
    - Lounsberry, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Moore, Fred, undated (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Tytla, Adrienne, undated (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Tytla, William: BRAVE LITTLE TAILOR, undated (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Tytla, William: COCK O' THE WALK, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Tytla, William: REASON AND EMOTION (Hitler sketchs), undated (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sequence #11-69, undated (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sequence #11-75, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - Devil sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Tytla, William: FANTASIA: Night on Bald Mountain - various sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Tytla, William: PINOCCHIO: Stromboli, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Tytla, William: SNOW WHITE: Dwarfs, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 146-147)
    - Tytla, William: Self-portraits and caricatures, undated (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Tytla, William: THE SULTAN'S CAT, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Tytla, William: Various sketches, undated (Box 4, Folder 150-151)
    - Tytla, William: Photos, undated (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Williams, Richard: Bloo (commercial art), undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Williams, Richard: A CHRISTMAS CAROL, undated (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Williams, Richard: Cresta (commercial art), undated (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Williams, Richard: Johnson and Johnson (commercial art), undated (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Williams, Richard: THE PINK PANTHER, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Williams, Richard: Tic-Tac (commercial art), undated (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Williams, Richard: TRANS-SIBERIAN EXPRESS, undated (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Williams, Richard: WHO FRAMED ROGER RABBIT, undated (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Williams, Richard: Various, undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
- Accretions 2003 - Series VI: Major Projects
  Access to Series VI Subseries A of the 2003 Accretion has been restricted by the collection donor. These files will become avaiable to researchers in March 2023.
  Series VI consists of research materials for major projects by Canemaker. Research notes, interview transcripts, correspondence and other related items used for specific projects by Canemaker are processed together to aid archival retrieval.
  - Subseries A: "The Art and Flair of Mary Blair"
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (draft manuscript), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (draft manuscript), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (edits and annotations), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS The Art and Flair of Mary Blair (research notes), undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Barrier, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Beckerman, Howard, undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Donovan, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Kevin, undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee - biographical material, undated (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence: Fred Cline, undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence: Walt Disney, undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Lee: Correspondence (misc), undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Lee Blair, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Walt Disney, undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: family, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Dick Irvine, undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Jacqueline Kennedy, undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Correspondence: Jack Lavin, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: House, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Interviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: News clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: Photographs (digital copies), undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Blair, Mary: South African Trip (Disney), undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Chamberlain, Jeanne, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cline, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cole Black and the Seven Drarves (musical with art by M.B.), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Cole Black and the Seven Drarves (cassette tape), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Crump, Roland, undated (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Davis, Marc, undated (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Disney, Roy, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Docter, Pete, undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Fujikawa, Gyo, undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Garner, Lou, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Giaimo, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Graver, Neil, undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Hench, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Hench, John, undated (Box 5, Folder Johnson, Michael)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Lefton, Wendy, undated (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Marling, Karal Ann, undated (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS O'Connor, Ken, undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Perine, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Rich, Maggie, undated (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Shue, Ken, undated (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - RESTRICTED ACCESS Sklar, Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 209)